<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="Event-B XText Basic Tutorial">
   <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Event-B XText Basic Tutorial" skip="false">
      <intro>
         <b>Introduction</b> This tutorial provides a step-by-step walk-through working with XEvent-B constructs.
      </intro>
      <onCompletion>
         <b>Conclusion</b> You should now be familiar with the syntax of XEvent-B constructs, i.e., XContexts and XMachines, and their compilation to Rodin constructs, i.e., Contexts and Machines. While the outer syntax is checked by XEvent-B, the inner syntax (e.g., within mathematical expressions and predicates) is checked at the Rodin Event-B level.
      </onCompletion>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 1. Customise the Event-B Explorer" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to customise the Event-B Explorer so that XEvent-B constructs are visible.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> Since the filter on &quot;All files and folders&quot; is now disabled, there might be other files and folders than XEvent-B constructs will also be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="CustomiseEventBExplorer.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 2. Create an Event-B Project" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to create an Event-B project for the XEvent-B constructs.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the project &quot;Club&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="CreateEventBProject.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 3. Create a simple XContext coursesCtx.bucx" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to create a simple XContext within the newly created project.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;coursesCtx.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Context &quot;coursesCtx&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="CreateCoursesCtx.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 4. Create a simple XMachine m0.bumx" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to create a simple XMachine within the newly created project.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XMachine&quot;m0.bumx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Machine &quot;m0&quot; (without any error) should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="CreateM0.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Task 5. Create extended XContexts" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to create some more extended XContexts within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContexts and the corresponding Rodin Contexts should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 5.1. Create a simple XContext membersCtx.bucx" skip="false">
            <intro>
               <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this sub-task is to create a simple XContext &quot;membersCtx.bucx&quot; within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;membersCtx.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Context &quot;membersCtx&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreateMembersCtx.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 5.2. Create an extended XContext participantsCtx.bucx" skip="false">
            <intro>
               <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this sub-task is to create an extended XContext &quot;participantsCtx.bucx&quot; within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;participantsCtx.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Context &quot;participantsCtx&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreateParticipantsCtx.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 5.3. Create an extended XContext instructorsCtx.bucx" skip="false">
            <intro>
               <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this sub-task is to create an extended XContext &quot;instructorsCtx.bucx&quot; within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;instructorsCtx.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Context &quot;instructorsCtx&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreateInstructorsCtx.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
      </taskGroup>
      <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Task 6. Create refined XMachines" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this task is to create some more refined XMachines within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XMachines and the corresponding Rodin Machines should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
         </onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 6.1. Create a refined XMachine m1.bumx" skip="false">
            <intro>
               <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this sub-task is to create a refined XMachine &quot;m1.bumx&quot; within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;m1.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Machine &quot;m1&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreateM1.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Task 6.2. Create a refined XMachine m2.bumx" skip="false">
            <intro>
               <b>Introduction</b> The purpose of this sub-task is to create a refined XMachine &quot;m2.bumx&quot; within the &quot;Club&quot; project.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               <b>Conclusion</b> By now, the XContext &quot;m2.bucx&quot; and the corresponding Rodin Machine &quot;m2&quot; should be visible in the Event-B Explorer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreateM2.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
      </taskGroup>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
